https://www.autotrainingcentre.com/privacy-policy/

F&I Manager Careers
Heavy Vehicle Systems (Basics and Advanced)
Heavy Vehicle Systems (Specialist)
About Us
Why ATC?
Privacy Policy
Automotive Training Centre is located in Richmond, BC, Canada. Access to the web site is free and anonymous. The privacy of visitors is of paramount importance to us. Cookies are used when entering our site to record the location where each visitor arrived from. This is used for tracking visitors which come from our affiliate sites.
Each web page access is recorded in a log file. The contents of the log file are analyzed each week and each month to determine how many visitors we serve, what pages they look at most, and from where they connect. This information may be shared with outside parties.
Visitors who purchase our products and become clients are entered into ours and possibly our clients’ database. The client information is used solely for billing purposes and for notifying the client of future updates to our products. The Information in the client database is not available for sale or other use by anyone outside of Automotive Training Centre. Similarly, the information of all visitors who join our affiliate program is never made available outside of Automotive Training Centre and its clients.
ATC will not collect personally identifiable information about you (that is your name, address, telephone number , or email address) unless you provide it voluntarily. If you do not want your personal identifiable information collected, do not submit it to us. if you do submit personally-identifiable information, we will use it in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: we will use to complete the contact or request, we may store and process that information to better understand your needs, and how we can improve our products and services, we may use that information to contact you. We will not give or sell your individual information to any outside company for its use in marketing or soliciting and we will maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and it will only be used to support your relationship with Automotive Training Centre.
If you have any questions about your privacy on our web sites, please contact us.
Automotive Training Centre.com,
210-13460 Smallwood Place
Richmond, BC V6V 1W8
Phone: 604.270.6121
Fax:
info@education-marketing.ca/atc
This statement discloses the privacy practices for Automotive Training Centre (“ATC”) and its websites www.AutomotiveTrainingCentre.com, www. AutoTrainingCentre.com, and www.ATCagent.com.
ATC Privacy Statement THIS AGREEMENT WAS LAST UPDATED ON DECEMBER 17TH 2003 Automotive Training Centre is firmly committed to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website, including the ATC agent and affiliate communities.
The protection of your privacy being very important, we have adopted the following practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. We will notify all registered users via email of any change to this Privacy Statement, unless you have opted-out of receiving email from us. From time to time, changes to this Privacy Statement will also be communicated on this site.
What information do you gather automatically from visitors?
We use your IP address (the series of numbers associated with your individual computer) to help us maintain our site and identify problems with our server. Your IP address does not disclose any personally revealing information about you.
We do use cookies to identify traffic that comes through advertising adn referrals, and to facilitate a more user friendly experience. Cookies are small pieces of information that a web site places on your computer’s hard drive so we know it’s you when you visit. This helps us to create a personalized experience for you when you visit our site. The use of cookies is a very common practice on the Internet. If you are uncomfortable with this, you can disable all cookies through your browser settings. Your enjoyment of our site won’t be affected if you have set your browser to reject cookies.
What information will you ask me for?
When you register to use any ATC service you will be asked for some general identifying information which will enable us to provide you with this individualized service. We gather contact information (like your email address), demographic information (like your city of residence or age). We may share some of this information for our own research purposes with our professional advisors or consultants and third party partners, however the information shared will be limited to non-personally identifying demographic information shared under cover of a confidentiality agreement. If you choose to enroll in a program, we collect financial information (like your credit card number and expiry date). We will only use this information in the course of providing our service to you.
When you request more information, depending on the nature of the inquiry or course or program which you choose, you will be asked for some personal to start or complete your enrollment process.
How will this information be used and who has access to it?
If you request any information from us, we may use your contact information to send you valuable updates and timely notices of promotions and course or program materials. Our site provides you with the opportunity to opt- out to receiving different types of communications from us at the point where we request registration information. You may modify this choice at any time by contacting ATC at the addresses below.
Your personally identifying and demographic information is used to personalize your request for information and/or enrolment process, and to deliver targeted advertising and promotional offers to you from external companies that are of the highest relevance to your demographic profile. Other than your e-mail or mailing address, your contact information is never available to other members or organizations.
In the event that you decide to enroll in a course or program, , you will be asked for your financial information (like credit card number) which can be read by others when you initiate your order as we may not use a secured system. You will know you are in secure mode when a tiny padlock icon – located at the bottom of your browser – appears “locked”. Otherwise you are in a non-secured environment and any information transmitted by this method may be collected or read by parties not related to ATC. It is recommended to transfer such information in a secured method.
The personally identifiable information we collect from you is used for internet review and to improve the content and functionality of our web server or course and program materials. The specific information we collect is not shared with other organizations and we will never release your personally identifiable information to an external organization without your prior consent except for the purposes of validating credit information and collecting debts, or unless we reasonably believe we are required to do so by operation of law.
How long do you keep the information I’ve given you?
We keep the information you have given us for until we have received a request from you stated otherwise.
Can I change the information I have already given you?
You can always verify or request the removal of the personally identifiable information we have collected by contacting ATC at the address below or from the main menu on the site.
Any such request may also be made by contacting the ATC Privacy Officer at the co-ordinates listed at the bottom of this page.
Advertisers
When you inquire about advertising opportunities on our site, you will be asked for contact information and information related to your advertising objectives. This information will be used to provide you with the business information you are seeking. Your information is only shared with internal staff and the external ad representation agencies that sell media space on the site, on our behalf. ATC sites may contain links to other sites not affiliated with ATC. Please note that these other sites may have privacy policies that differ from those of ATC. We have no control over any personal information that you provide to these sites.
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices contact ATC.
Associates, Agents and Affiliates
When you register to become an associate, affiliate, or agent of our site, you will be asked for contact information and information related to your site. Your information will only be used by internal staff and may be shared with parties external to the company without your consent. Your information will be used to secure your approval as an Affiliate, Associate or Agent, to facilitate communication between our two sites and to send you payment, based on your site’s performance.
Contacting us for privacy issues ONLY **Please note that this phone number will NOT connect you to a customer service representative.**
ALL OTHER ENQUIRIES SHOULD BE SENT TO info at autotrainingcentre. com
QUICK LINKS
About Us
Why ATC?
Yes, I agree to receive messages about Automotive Training Centre. You may withdraw your consent to receive these messages at any time.
Heavy Vehicle Systems (Basics and Advanced)
Heavy Vehicle Systems (Specialist)
Automotive Training Centre © 2020 | All rights reserved. | SITE MAP | PRIVACY POLICY
Please wait! Form is submitting...
Request Information
